Arash Gholami, IT Service Desk Analyst - Technical

925-759-9550, arashgholami1990@gmail.com

P	R	O	F	I	LE
---	---	---	---	---	----

Customer and Employee Oriented. Cooperatively works well with others to complete tasks in an efficient and professional manner. Demonstrated skills in mentoring peers and assisting with training needs. able to properly convey job information and apply related concepts and theories to the task at hand.

6+ Years of Direct Healthcare IT experience and demonstrated working knowledge of technical support infrastructure of ApeX and Epic Systems.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Oct 2013 — Feb 2020

Business Support Analyst II, UCSF Benioff Children's Hospital - Oakland

Oakland,CA

- Analyzed incoming phone calls and diagnosed the computer and software needs as well as referred support
 requests to the appropriate staff.
- Provided technical support on desktop PCs, printers, wireless devices, and software applications, both networked and local. Identified and escalated problem calls as appropriate.
- Addressed a full range of customer needs, including trouble-shooting, technical assistance, system usage support, password reset, and installation, move, and change request.
- Provided first point of support for all incoming calls while managed Ques.
- Documented each end users support claim and provided support in a clear and understandable format, documented all resolution for tickets which clear instruction to be used for future training.
- Managed users account using Microsoft active directory, SMS console tools and remote tools.

Jun 2013 - Jan 2014

Help Desk Consultant, Portable CIO

Alamo, CA

- Assumed rollout responsibilities. Maintained desktop images and supported PC rollout process, including
 installation of current operating systems, hospital specific software and peripheral devices for over 4,000
 end users.
- · Maintained Printer Configuration and supported Printer rollout process, including IP configuration.

2012 - 2014

Relocation Technician, Murphy McKay and Associates

Lafayette, CA

- Functioned collaboratively with various partners(Juniper).
- · Rollout Responsibility of taking down computers and desk and re-assembling after moving
- Worked within a server room setting up connecting servers
- Provided excellent cable manage to avoid any hazards

EDUCATION

2009 — 2013 Diablo Valley College

Pleasant Hill, CA

Computer Information System

SKILLS

Apex Technical Knowledge

Experienced JavaScript, SQL data base, and C++ programming

Skillful

Epic System Technical

d Experienced

ServiceNow Ticketing Software

Expert

LANGUAGES

Farsi

Knowledge

Native speaker